[
    {
        "question": "Hi, I'm a new student. ____ name's Maria",
        "answers": [ " " ],
        "correctAnswer": "My"
    },
    {
        "question": "This is my friend Anna. ____ mother is my teacher",
        "answers": [ " " ],
        "correctAnswer": "Her"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who are you? What's ____ name",
        "answers": [ " " ],
        "correctAnswer": "your"
    },
    {
        "question": "We love English, and Mr Forester, the English teacher is  ____ favorite teacher",
        "answers": [ " " ],
        "correctAnswer": "Our"
    },   
    {
        "question": "Scott and Stephen are my cousins.  ____ modher is my aunt",
        "answers": [ " " ],
        "correctAnswer": "Their"
    },   
    {
        "question": "Thist is my father. _____ name is John.",
        "answers": [ "His", "He's" ],
        "correctAnswer": "His"
    },
    {
        "question": "Thist is my father. _____ 40 years old.",
        "answers": [ "His", "He's", "He are" ],
        "correctAnswer": "He's"
    },  
    {
        "question": "A: This is Mary. B: ____ two cousins? A:no, ____.We're sisters.Mary's twelve yearsold. ",
        "answers": [ "Are you / are", "You are / aren't", "Are you / aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "Are you / aren't"
    },
    {
        "question": "Henry ___ fifteen years old. He ___ only ten.",
        "answers": [ "are / is","isn't / is", "are / aren't", "isn't / aren't"],
        "correctAnswer": "isn't / is"
    },
    {
        "question": "this is my new tablet and this is my new mobile phone. ___ my new gadgets.",
        "answers": [ "We're", "they're" ],
        "correctAnswer": "they're"
    },
    {
        "question": "A: What year ____ you in? B: We ___ in year 5.",
        "answers": [ "are , am", "is , am", "are , are", "is , are" ],
        "correctAnswer": "are , are"
    },


    {
        "question": "My brother ____ very good at math, but ___ .",
        "answers": [ "is , I am not", "is , aren't", "are , I am not", "are , aren't" ],
        "correctAnswer": "is , I am not"
    },


    {
        "question": " ____you a geography teacher? No, I ___ a history teacher." ,
        "answers": [ "Is , are", "Is , am ", "Are , are", "Are , am" ],
        "correctAnswer": "Are , am"
    }


]